实际上是双方的问题
Actually it's both.
史卓德·马丁这样说  纽曼那么说
Strother Martin says it one way, Newman another. But, yes.
都是演员
现在我给你们30秒
Now I'm going to give you 30 seconds to say
说说你们对彼此的看法  真正吼出来
what you think of each other-- to really blow it out
然后我们再也不提它
into the open--and then we're burying that crap forever.
-谁先来  -我来
- Who wants to go first-- - May I?
比尔是个自大狂  贪婪  危险
Bill is ego-maniacal. Greedy. Dangerous.
无礼  幼稚
Crude. Juvenile--
"美元大亨"比尔
Okay. Dollar Bill--
你是个自命不凡的  搔首弄姿的混蛋
You're a pretentious, preening ass.
你是个寄生虫  你根本不赚钱
You're a parasite. You're not an earner.
狗皮膏药广告  没种
You're a page pusher. You got no balls.
你不是个男人  这不是性别歧视
You're less than a man-- and that's not sexist
因为你也比不上所有
because you're less than any woman I've ever shared
-女同事  -停
- a trading desk with-- - Stop.